So, Jones, Tanaka and Muller are all family names.
Então, Jones, Tanaka e Müller são nomes de família.
I got them from a database, of common family names in different countries.
Eu os obtive em um banco de dados de nomes comuns de família em países diferentes.
Jones is one of the most common family names in the U.S. and
Jones é um dos nomes de família mais comuns nos Estados Unidos,
in England, and Wales.
na Inglaterra e no Países de Gales.
Tanaka is one of the most common family names in Japan.
Tanaka é um dos nomes de família mais comuns no Japão.
And Muller, is one of the most common family names in Germany and Austria.
E Müller é um dos nomes de família mais comuns na Alemanha e na Áustria.
But Mary J.Washington, isn't a family name, it's a person's full name.
Mas Mary J.Washington não é um nome de família, é o nome todo de uma pessoa.
We wouldn't expect to see a single database column,
Não esperaríamos ver uma única coluna de banco de dados
that held full names for some rows, and just family names for other rows.
que tivesse nomes completos em algumas linhas e apenas nomes de família em outras.
So Mary J.Washington is the correct answer.
Por isso, Mary J.Washington é a resposta certa.
So here we've seen that when we think about pieces of data that might be in
Aqui vimos que quando pensamos em dados que poderiam estar em
a database, we have to think not only about their type, but
um banco de dados, temos que pensar não apenas no tipo, mas
also their meaning, what they represent in the real world.
também no significado, o que eles representam no mundo real.